#### Contact

harriswatson@msn.com

www.linkedin.com/in/nicolewatson-a972a321 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Inpatient Case Managment

### Certifications

Certified Dementia Practioner

QAPI Certified Professional (QCP)

Wound Care Certification

# Nicole Watson

**Director of Nursing** 

Lancaster, Pennsylvania Area

## Summary

Experienced Director Of Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Customer Service, Medicaid, Case Management, and Medicare. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate's degree focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Lancaster General College of Nursing and Health Sciences.

## Experience

Pleasant View Retirement Community Director Of Nursing July 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month) Manheim, Pennsylvania

Pleasant View Retirement Community 4 years 1 month

Assistant Director of Nursing May 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 3 months) Manheim, PA

RN Unit Manager July 2012 - May 2015 (2 years 11 months) Manheim

Lancaster General Health Social Worker June 1999 - November 2003 (4 years 6 months)

## Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration, Healthcare Management (2020 - 2022)

Lancaster General College of Nursing and Health Sciences
Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)

Juniata College Bachelor of Social Work, Social Work · (1995 - 1999)